[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":48060,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":51688,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure tha t when w e combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":8399,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":60088,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":4584,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":64673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":1239,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":65913,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0. 3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":3616,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":69529,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1960,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":71489,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3471,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":74960,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":4031,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":78992,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["3","2"],"rt":5104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":84096,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub> 6</sub>  1 = 2 because 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":880,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":84976,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["4","3"],"rt":4152,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":89129,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":894,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":90024,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you sta rt with  the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2872,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":92896,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":873,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":93769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":2599,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":96369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":792,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":97161,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":2208,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":99369,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1015,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":100385,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":9897,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":110282,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1022,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":111305,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger , you su btract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3047,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":114352,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":825,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":115178,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":134743,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":249922,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":21334,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":271257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":13368,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":284625,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1016,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":285641,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":2567,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":288209,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":777,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":288986,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is t he inver se of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":1815,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":290801,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":719,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":291521,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":1489,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":293010,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":704,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":293714,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":2799,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":296513,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":4192,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":300705,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":33401,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":334106,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> under +<sub>6</sub>. <br  /><br />  However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":37447,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":371553,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":4207,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":375761,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":12895,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":388657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2936,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":391594,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":1455,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":393049,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 4  a genera tor under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"Yes","response_history":["Yes"],"rt":1839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":394889,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1431,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":396321,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":1927,"trial_type":"ques tion","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":398249,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1807,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":400056,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete  the rema ining questions as accurately as possible.","rt":10665,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":410722,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3952,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":414674,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":88255,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":502929,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":3903,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":506833,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":2736,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":509569,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":2423,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":511993,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4672,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":516665,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":2480,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":519145,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I didn't have to subtract.","response_history":["5. The number ","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I left the ","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I left the","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I left th","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I left t","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I left ","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I left","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I lef","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I le","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I l","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so I didn't have to subtract/","5. The numbers added came out to less than 9 so  I didn't  have to subtract."],"rt":51991,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":571137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3. The numbers added up to 12 so I subtracted 9 from 12.","response_history":["3. The numbers a","3. The numbers added up tp","3. The numbers added up to 12 so I subtracted 9 from 12."],"rt":21072,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":592210,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0. I think the identity was whatever number you'd get when you get the same number as +9.","response_history":["0. I think iut ","0. I think iut","0. I think iu","0. I th ink it w as the n","0. I think it was t","0. I think it","0. I think i","0. I think the identity was whatever number that would be ","0. I think the identity was whatever number w","0. I think the identity was whatever number you'd get when r","0. I think the identity was whatever number you'd get when u","0. I think the identity was whatever number you'd get when you get the same number as +9."],"rt":124008,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":716218,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":8253,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":724473,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":2048,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":726521,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":4152,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":730673,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6. 6 plus 3 would be 9 so 6 is the inverse.","response_history":["6. 6 plus w","6. 6 plus 3 th","6. 6 plus 3 t","6. 6 plus 3 would be 9 so 7","6. 6 plus 3 would be 9 so 6 is the inverse."],"rt":16855,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":747529,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in wo rds how  you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. I don't really remember the generator rules.","response_history":["2","No. ","Yes. I think because you c","Yes. I think because you g","Yes. I think because you ","Yes. I think because you","Yes. I think because yo","Yes. I think because y","Yes. I think because 2 plus 2 is 4 and you can e","Yes. I think because 2 plus 2 is 4 and you can get to 9 using 1's","Yes. I think because 2 plus 2 is 4 and you can get to 9 using 1'","No. I don't really remm","No. I don't really remember the generator rules."],"rt":89656,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":837186,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Yes. 3+3+3 would equal 9.","response_history":["Yes,","Yes. 3 p","Yes.  3 ","Ye s. 3=3=","Yes. 3=3","Yes. 3=","Yes. 3+3+3 would equal 9."],"rt":19430,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":856618,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. I cannot explain my answer as I don't really understand the generator rules well.","response_history":["No. I","No. i","No. I cannoy e","No. I cannoy ","No. I cannoy","No. I cannot explain my answer as I don't fee","No. I cannot explain my answer as I don't fe","No. I cannot explain my answer as I don't f","No. I cannot explain my answer as I don't really underat","No. I cannot explain my answer as I don't really undera","No. I cannot explain my answer as I don't really understand the e","No. I cannot explain my answer as I don't really understand the gee","No. I cannot explain my answer as I don't really unde rstand t he generator rules well."],"rt":27726,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":884346,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No. I don't understand the rules well enough to say.","response_history":["Yes.","Yes","Ye","Y","No. I o","No. I don't understand the rules well enough to say."],"rt":15422,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":899769,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some questions about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":51887,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":951657,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"1+2n 2= ","response_history":["1+2n 2= ","1+2n2= ","1+2n 2= "],"rt":194287,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":1145945,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I have no idea.","response_history":["I have no idea."],"rt":10144,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":1156090,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n </sub> w ithout seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I'm not sure how you'd get the generator without knowing the value first.","response_history":["I' ","I'm not sure how you'd get the generator without knowing the value first."],"rt":98046,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":1254137,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":4877,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":1259017,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":3995,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":1263012,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["False"],"rt":3404,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":1266417,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"False. Just because it is multiple of a divisor doesn't necessarily mean it is a generator.","response_history":["False. Just because it is a divisor doesn't  neccess aril ","False. Just because it is a divisor doesn't neccessarily me","False. Just because it is a divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is ma divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is mla divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is mlua divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is mluia divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is mlua divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is mla divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is ma divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is mua divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is mula divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is multa divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is multia divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is multipa divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is multiplea divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because i t is mul tiple a divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is multiple oa divisor doesn't necessarily me","False. Just because it is multiple of a divisor doesn't necessarily mean it is a generator."],"rt":348039,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":1614457,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":11766,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":1626225,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"sometimes","response":"Sometimes, if it's a lower number I think it can be a generator but the higher it gets it may no longer work as one.","response_history":["Sometimes, if it's a lower number I think it can be a generator but the higher it gets t ","Sometimes, if it's a lower number I think it can be a generator but the higher it gets t","Sometimes, if it's a lower number I think it can be a generator but the higher it gets it may no longer work.","Sometimes, if it's a lower number I think it can be a generator but the higher it gets it may no longer work as one."],"rt":50104,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":1676330,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Ne ver","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":31741,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":1708073,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your background. Please press Continue to continue.","rt":1959,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":1710033,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"29","response_history":["29"],"rt":2414,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":1712447,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"High school diploma","response_history":["High school diploma"],"rt":2858,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":1715305,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most advanced math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I think just a basic high school math class which is obvious based on my responses here.","response_history":["I think just  ","I think just a basic high school math class. ","I think just a basic high school math class.","I think just a basic high school math class which wi","I think just a basic high school math class which w","I think just a basic high school math class which is obvious bases o","I think just a basic high school math class which is obvious bases ","I think just a basic high school math class which is  obvious  bases","I think just a basic high school math class which is obvious based on m ","I think just a basic high school math class which is obvious based on my respone","I think just a basic high school math class which is obvious based on my responses here."],"rt":27775,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":1743081,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":2927,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":1746008,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathemati cal grou p?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":3248,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":1749256,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2534,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":1751792,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - n ot at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2224,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":1754016,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"3 - definitely","response_history":["2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"rt":3232,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":1757248,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1345,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":1758593,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages  spoken i n your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":3500,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":1762094,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":2481,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":1764575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I was pretty confused with the latter parts of the hit but I did try. I enjoyed trying to learn about the rules even if I didn't do very well.","response_history":["Ih","I hope t","I hope ","I ho","I h","I was pretty confused tow","I was pretty confused to","I was  pretty  confused t","I was pretty confused with the latter parts of the hit and I hope my ","I was pretty confused with the latter parts of the hit and I h","I was pretty confused with the latter parts of the hit but I did try. I enjoyed trying to learn about the rules even if I didn't do very well."],"rt":47986,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":1812562,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]